performbetter.com 2017-12-02

# Perform Better Privacy Policy

M-F Athletic/Perform Better is aware of our customers' need for privacy while ordering on the Internet. It is our intention to make our sites as secure as commercially reasonable, while offering the comfort and convenience of on-line ordering to our customers. However technology is constantly changing, by utilizing our site, you understand and accept any risks that could occur through electronic information sharing through any of our sites, even though advertised as secure. We are making every effort to ensure that our customers have the most private ordering processes available, but we cannot be held responsible for unforeseen or unintended access to our client information.

If you require privacy over and above our secure site structure or have a specific question you would like to ask concerning the extent of privacy afforded by any of our sites, please contact us via email at [performbetter@mfathletic.com](mailto:performbetter@mfathletic.com), or call us toll-free at 1-888-556-7464, Monday through Friday, 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. E.S.T. We will be happy to address any concerns you might have from ordering on-line.

M-F Athletic/Perform Better will not and does not release personal identifiable information about our customers, at any time, through any means, to any vendors, or other third parties without your permission (unless it is necessary for the completion of your order). Personal identifiable information includes information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, which is unique to you. Anonymous information such as site usage information, domain names and/or I.P. addresses or browsers visiting our sites, is utilized for site visitation tracking information, and is aimed at bettering our presentation of site pages to our customers.

## Registering On Our Sites

We wish to assure you that when you register on any of our sites, the personal information you enter is secure, and is utilized internally for order processing, but may include some private mailings to you, our customers. If you wish to be excluded from our mailing lists, please indicate via email to: [performbetter@mfathletic.com](mailto:performbetter@mfathletic.com). We will be happy to comply with your request.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or write a review.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * \- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * \- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * \- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * \- To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

  * \- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving requests for product reviews or ratings.

  * \- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

##  How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

##  Do we use cookies? 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone. 

We also use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to help us gather additional information about your visit to our website.

## Google Analytics & Remarketing

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitor use this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. No personally identifiable information is collected about you. The anonymous information generated by Google Analytics cookies about your use of this website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then processed to compile statistical reports on website activity for PerformBetter.com only. We use these reports to evaluate aggregate visitor usage so that we can optimize the content, and its marketing, to better meet customer needs.

We have implemented Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We utilize non-personal identifiable, 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender and interests with Google Analytics to better analyze the demographics of our site users in order to better serve our customers.

We may implement Remarketing with Google Analytics and other vendors to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. We are

We may implement Google Display Network Impression Reporting. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website.

Learn more about Google's Advertising Policies [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can use [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en) to manage the Google ads you see. Finally, you can [manage cookies in your web browser](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/managing/).

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##  California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their their account and going to the 'Personal Information' page.

##  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

##  CAN-SPAM Compliance 

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

##  Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **November 24, 2013**

##  Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

1600 Division Road  
West Warwick, RI 02893  
USA  
888-556-7464

##  Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * \- Federal Trade Commission Fair
  * \- California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * \- Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
  * \- Privacy Alliance
  * \- Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
  * \- Trust Guard Privacy Requirements
